Allan Marquand Papers, 1858-1951 (bulk 1878-1950): Finding Aid C0269
Manuscripts Division
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1872-1924; 1950-1951; 9 boxes
  - Morris, Charles D, 1881; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Morris, George S. (1840-1889), 1879-1880; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Morse, Edward Sylvester (1838-1925), 1902; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Mortimer, Richard, 1912; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Mortimer, Stanley, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Mudie's Select Library, Ltd, 1911; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Murray, A. S, 1890-1891; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Murray, J. O, 1876; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Nassau Literary Magazine, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - National Amateur Gymnastic, 1873; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - National Hide and Leather Bank, 1893; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - National Lecture Bureau, 1873; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - The New Jersey Historical Society, 1888-1912; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - New York School Journal and Educational News, 1875; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Newall, N, 1911; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Nicole, G. de, 1919-1924; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Nicoll, Delancey (1854-1931), 1873-1874; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - North, H. E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Norton, Charles Eliot (1827-1908), 1886-1895; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Norton, Richard, 1899; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Nottingham City Museum & Art Gallery, 1918; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - O'Reilly, Mary B, 1902; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Olyphant, Robert, 1870-1872; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Ormand, A. T, 1979; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Osborn, Henry Fairfield (1857-1935), 1886-1922; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Osgood, James R. (1836-1892), 1876-1877; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Packard, W. A, 1876-1881; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Parker, Charles P., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Parmly, Duncan D, 1873-1878; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Parqui, W, 1921; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Parrott, R. D. H, 1871; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Parsons, Anna Reed (Mrs. W. B. Parsons), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Paterson, William, 1876; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Paton, David, 1875; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Patton, Francis Landey (1843-1932), 1890-1901; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Pearson, Richmond (1852-1923), 1873; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Peirce, Charles Sanders (1839-1914), 1886; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Pencil Points, 1923; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Perkins, F. Mason, 1913-1917; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Peterson, James B, 1902; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Petrie, Hilda F, 1901; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Plagair, Edith, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Plaisted, Henry, 1877; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Platt, Dan Fellows, 1918; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Poland, Reginald, 1922; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Porter, Arthur Kingsley (1883-1933), 1918-1920; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Porter, Eliphalet Nott (1836-1901), 1886; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Post, Chandler R. (1881-1959), 1911-1922; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Potter, Mrs, 1875; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Pratt, Waldo S. (1857-1939), 1911; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Prentice, William K, 1900-1922; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Preston, T. J., Jr., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Prime, William Cowper (1925-1905), 1886; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Princeton Alumni Association, 1876; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Princeton Architectural Association, 1922; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Princeton Battle Monument, 1902-1922; 4 folders (Box 17, Folder 48-51)
  - Princeton Battle Monument (Frederick MacMonnies), 1894-1919; 3 folders (Box 18, Folder 1-3)
    ALsS by and to Marquand
  - Princeton Battle Monument (War Dept.), 1914-1922; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 4)
    U.S. Engineer Office
  - Princeton Battle Monument, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Princeton Dancing Class, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Princeton University, Alex Leitch, 1950; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Princeton University Art Museum, 1917-1921; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Princeton University, Class of '74, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Princeton University Department of Art and Archaeology Unidentified, 1951; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 10)
    re: Allan Marquand
  - Princeton University Graduate College, 1913; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Princeton University Library, 1924; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 12)
    Lawrence Heyl
  - Princeton University Press, 1912-1921; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Princeton University School of Architecture, 1922; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Princeton University Sesquicentennial, 1896; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Publio, Podio, 1892; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Puchstein, O, 1891; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Putzel, Charles, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Pyne, Moses Taylor (1855-1921), 1900-1902; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Rafard (Fernand Robert), 1893; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Reed, S. A, 1913; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Relavalle, S. Busset, de, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Rendall, William Stewart, 1903; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Revue de L'Art Chrétien, 1912; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Reymond, Marcel, 1896-1910; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Richardson, Ernest C. (1860-1939), 1922; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Richter, [? ], 1893; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Riordan, Roger (1848-1904), 1902; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Rivoiza, G. T, 1906-1909; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Robertson, Hugh C, 1889; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Robinson, Edward (1858-1931), 1901-1917; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Robinson, Sir John Charles (1824-1913), 1892-1894; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Rogers & Manson, 1902; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Rooseboom, M. P., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Rorison, A. B. St. Clair, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Royce, Josiah (1855-1916), 1880; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Rubinstein, Stella, 1921; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Ryan, Thomas Fortune (1858-1928), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Sachs, Paul J. (1878-1965), 1922; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Saint Gaudens, Augustus (1848-1907), 1888-1895; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Sanford, E. C. A., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Sandys, Sir John Edwin (1844-1922), 1905; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Saratoga Rowing Assn, 1874; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Sargent, John Singer (1856-1925), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Schaff, David Schley (1852-1941), 1876; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Schenck, W. E, 1878; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Scognamiglio--Fratelli Scognamiglio, 1893; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Scott, W. B, 1876; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Scott, William Berryman (1858-1947), 1900; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Scribner, Charles (1854-1930), 1878-1981; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Scribner's Magazine, 1912; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Scudder, Willard, 1921; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Sedgwick, Henry (1838-1900), 1896; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Seeber, B, 1912; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Sella-Rey, Clotilda, 1915; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Shapley, John, 1913-1914; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Shaw, Quincy A, 1893; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Shear, Theodore Leslie (1880-1945), 1922; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Sheldon, Edward W, 1910; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Sheldon, George, 1877; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Sheldon, George William (1843-1914), 1876; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Sheldon, Theodore (1853-1905), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Sherman, Frederic Fairchild (1874?-1940), 1912; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Shields, Charles Woodruff (1825-1904), 1873-1876; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Sigorini, L, 1901; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Siren, Oswald (1879-1966), 1914-1917; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Sloane, William Milligan (1850-1928), 1883-1921; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Smith, Cecil, 1911; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Smith, E. Baldwin (1888-1956), 1911-1922; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Smith, E. Munroe (1854-1926), 1881; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Smith, G. I. Murray, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Smith, H. A. Hammond, 1909; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Smith, Katherine E, 1887; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 74)
    Alex Masterton-1886; Susan N. Carter
  - Smith, Leigh Richmond, 1873-1875; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Smith, W. Scuyler, 1902; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1902; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Speyer, Sir Edgar (1862-1932), 1916; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Stern, George W, 1891; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Stewart, John A. (1822-1926), 1886-1892; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Stockton, Bayard, 1876-1915; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Stockton, C. J, 1875; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Stohlman, W. Frederick, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Sturgis & Walton Company, 1912; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Sturgis, Russell (1836-1909), 1886-1899; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Supino, B, 1903; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - Swift, Thomas Delano, 1871; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Swarzenski, Georg (1876-1957), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Taft, Charles P. (1843-1929), 1912; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Tarbell, J. B, 1909; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Townsend, Horace (1859-1922), 1919; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Trask, Katrina (1853-1922), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Trask, Spencer (1844-1922), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Turner, Charles, 1887; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Turnure, Arthur B, 1876; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - United States Embassy--London, 1896; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 8)
    Bayard, Thomas F., 1828-1898
  - United States Treasury Department, 1892; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - United States Trust Co. of New York, 1912; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Universal Masonry, 1911; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - University of California Berkeley, 1924; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - University of Pennsylvania Department of Archaeology & Paleontology, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Valentiner, W. R. (1880-1958), 1910-1911; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Van Doren, P. A. V, 1912; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Van Dyke, Henry (1852-1933), 1873-1920; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Van Dyke, John Charles (1856-1932), 1922; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Van Dyke, Paul (1859-1933), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Van Lewey, Frederick, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Vanderbilt, George O, 1876-1877; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - VanDerlip, John R. (1860-1935), 1919; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Venn, John (1834-1923), 1881-1886; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Venturi, Adolfo (1856-1941), 1911-1924; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Villegas, José (1848-1921), 1892; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Vinton, Frederick (1817-1890), 1876; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Vitry, P, 1913; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Vogüe, E. Melchior de, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Vonkienbusch, Carl Otto, 1923; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - W. A. Mansell & Co, 1885; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - W. C. Hughes, 1886-1887; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Walsen, G, 1917; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Walston (Waldstein), Sir Charles (1856-1927), 1885-1909; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Walters, H, 1912; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Warbeke, John Martyn (1879-1950), 1902; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Ward, Clarence, 1922; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Ward, J.R. Wendel, 1923; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Ward, Thomas Humphrey, 1901-1902; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Ward William, 1882; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Ward, William H, 1893; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Ware, William R, 1891-1901; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Warren, H. Langford (1857-1917), 1906; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Watts, M. S, 1911; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Webb, Alexander Stewart (1835-1911), 1879; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Wells, Newell Woolsey (1851- ), 1875-1876; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - West, Andrew Fleming (1853-1943), 1909-1924; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - White, Anna H.B., 1887-1888; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Whitehead, Philip B, 1911; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Whiting, G, 1922; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Wilcox, A. M, 1886; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Williams, R. E, 1916; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Williams, Talcott (1849-1928), 1892; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Willis & Clements, 1885; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Wilson, Woodrow Thomas (1856-1924), 1900-1924; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Winship, Sam C, 1871; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Winslow, William Copley (1840-1925), 1886; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Winthrop, Grenville Lindall, 1912; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Wood, William, 1886; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Woods, Henry M, 1911; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Worcester Art Museum, 1918; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Wright, Jane, 1913-1922; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Wright, John Henry (1852-1908), 1886; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Wyckoff, W. A. (1865-1908), 1900; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Young, J. Donald, 1920; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Zug, George B., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Unidentified Correspondence, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 19, Folder 65)
- Series 3: Documents, 1871-1922; 5 boxes
  This series consists primarily of bills and receipts, degrees and commendations, and miscellaneous certificates.
  Organized into two suberies: loose documents and scrapbooks. The scrapbooks are arranged chronologically.
  - Subseries 3A: General, 1871-1912; 2 boxes
    Consists of financial documents, certificates, resolutions, and anmeldungs.
    - Anmeldungs, 1877; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 1)
      Buch, der Königlichen Friedrich-Wilhelms, Universität zu Berlin
    - Financial, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Certificates, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Resolutions, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Documents, 1871-1912; 1 folder (Box 20, Folder 5)
      Princeton grade reports (1871-1873), Y.M.C.A. membership card (1912), receipt for gold medal, Trophy Hall, University Gymnasium (1907)
    - Oversize Documents, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 53)
      Including: Ph.D. from Johns Hopkins University, assorted honorary degrees and commendations presented to Allan Marquand and Eleanor Cross Marquand, Episcopalian wedding contract between Allan Marquand and Eleanor Cross, drawing of Princeton University Gym
  - Subseries 3B: Scrapbooks of Receipts and Bills, 1883-1922; 3 boxes
    Consists of scrapbooks filled with receipts and bills.
    Not arranged according to any arrangement scheme.
    - Receipts and Bills, 1883-1922; 3 boxes (Box 21, Box 22, Box 23)
      4 scrapbooks
- Series 4: Photographs, undated; 3 boxes
  This series richly documents Princeton University buildings and grounds during Marquand's tenure, but also includes photographs of paintings, book, and manuscripts the Marquands collected, and a large photograph album.
  The photographs are organized into three subseries: one for groupings of family, friends, and Princeton photographs, one for other photographs of paintings and manuscripts owned by the Marquands, and one for the Marquand's personal photograph album.
  - Subseries 4A: Family, Friends, and Princeton, undated; 1 box
    Consists of photographs of Allan Marquand, his family, friends, Guernsey Hall (Princeton), and Princeton University during the time of his tenure.
    Arranged by subject of photographs.
    - Marquand, Allan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Marquand Family Photographs (including Eleanor Cross Marquand), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Marquand, Henry Gurdon (1819-1902), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Princeton Friends, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Evelyn College, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 5)
      Home of Allan Marquand, circa 1888
    - Guernsey Hall (Princeton), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Yaddo", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Princeton University and Buildings in the Princeton Area (1), dates not examined; 1 box
      - 1874 Boathouse on the canal (4), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Assorted medals, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Assorted medals, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
        pencil notes suggest athletic prizes of W. C. Dohn '90
      - Bonner-Marquand Gymnasium from southeast, with University Hotel visible to left, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Bonner-Marquand Gymnasium from southwest, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Championship Lacrosse Team, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - The Cannon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Chancellor Green, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Chapel (not on campus), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Dickinson Hall I, with two girls in front, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Dod Hall, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - E. M. Museum interior, in east wing of Nassau Hall (2), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
        mislabeled Guyot Hall
      - Garden, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Garden path, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
        unidentified
      - Halsted Observatory, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Marquand Chapel, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Marquand Chapel and Murray Hall from west, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Marquand Chapel burning (4), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Marquand Chapel burning, from east looking through nave to west front, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Marquand Chapel from west, McCosh visible to right, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Marquand Chapel and Murray Hall from west, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - McCosh Memorial Plaque from interior of the Marquand Chapel (2), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Murray Hall from north, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Murray Hall interior, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - The Museum of Historic Art, Brown visible to the right, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - School of Science, Class of 1877 Biological Laboratory to right, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - School of Science drafting class (the basis for engraving used in Marquand article), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Schoool of Science laboratory, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Stony Brook, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
        according to note on verso
      - Trinity Church (4), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - University Hotel from the northwest; Halsted Observatory visible to right, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Witherspoon Hall, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - Working Observatory and Professor Young's house (from south side of Prospect), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
      - reproduction after the selected proposal for An Art School for Princeton College by A. Page Brown, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Princeton University and Buildings in the Princeton Area (2), dates not examined; 1 box
      - 1874 Boathouse on the canal, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Bonner-Marquand Gymnasium, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Chancellor Green, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Cider press's sketch in plaster for drinking fountain by Thos. Shields Clarke, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
        according to notes
      - Clio, with Museum of Historic Art behind, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Dickinson Hall of Horrors?, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - E. M. Museum in Nassau Hall, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
        mislabeled Guyot Hall on verso
      - Falsted Observatory, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Guyot Memorial Plaque, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
        once in Marquand Chapel
      - Henry House?, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Lenox Library at the Seminary (2), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Maclean House (3), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Nassau Hall and Old Chapel, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Princeton Cemetery, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Prospect Houses, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Princeton aerial view, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Rockefeller Madison College doorway, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
        Hamilton Hall according to pencil notes
      - School of Science, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - School of Science laboratory, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - School of Science north facade, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - School of Science west facade (3), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - School of Science, professor's house, Dickinson Hall, Chancellor Green, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Students attending lecture, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
        history lecture according to notes on verso
      - Walkway, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Witherspoon Hall, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Witherspoon Hall, Bonner-Marquand and Reunion visible to left (2), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Witherspoon Hall, Reunion visible to left, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
      - Working Observatory and Professor Young's house, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Subseries 4B: Paintings, Prints, Books, Manuscripts, etc., undated; 1 box
    Consists of photographs of objects belonging to both Allan Marquand and his wife, Eleanor Cross Marquand.
    - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 25)
      photographs of objects belonging to both Allan Marquand and his wife, Eleanor Cross Marquand
  - Subseries 4C: Photograph Album, undated; 1 box
    Consists of photographs of Princeton buildings, grounds, and classmates.
    - Album, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 51)